# MUHAMADHENDRIK

#### **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

Bogor, West Java, Indonesia

+62812-8602-9281

muhamadhendrikbsns@gmail.com

#### PROFILE SUMMARY

I am someone who is interested in programming. I have experience in web and API development mainly using Laravel. I am very enthusiastic to learn new things and I am very motivated to always develop my potential. I can communicate well and I am able to work individually or in a team.

### PROFESSIONAL SKILL

PHP MySQL

PostgreSQL

Docker

Node JS

Laravel

**JQuery** 

Bootstrap

Redis

Go

# **EDUCATION**

## **Software Engineering**

Wikrama Vocational Highschool Bogor

2018 - 2021

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Back End & Web Developer**

#### PT. Anilo Adikarya Sentosa, South Jakarta

- Development and Maintenance Website and API Satwagia Indonesia
  - https://satwagia.app
  - API satwagia orderaja
  - Develop with Laravel, JQuery, MySQL
- Development and Maintenance Website Tukang Bersih Indonesia
  - https://dashboard.tukangbersih.com/
  - Develop with Laravel, JQuery, MySQL
- Integration with third parties (shipper) for shipping goods
- Integration with third parties (eweb) for accounting records
- · Sharing knowledge / training with client

#### **Back End & Web Developer**

July, 2021 - Feb, 2022

Feb, 2022 - July, 2023

#### PT. Robust Creative Media, Bogor

- Development website company profile with Laravel Framework, MySQL
  - https://sintera.id/
- Development ERP system with Lumen & Quasar, MySQL
  - https://vms.cnb.co.id

- Development POS system or Cashier with Laravel, JQuery, MySQL
  - o https://adminin.online/admin
  - o https://cashier.robust.web.id
- Development Foodstall Startup at Malaysia with Laravel, JQuery, MySQL
  - https://foodstall.app/
- Development Learning Management System with Laravel and JQuery, MySQL
  - https://koas.robust.web.id
- · Pertamina insurance website maintenance with PHP, MySQL
  - o https://tugu.ptdtsu.id
- Develop a multi-level marketing website for UMKM with Laravel, MySql, JQuery
  - o https://foodmate.id

# **Web Developer**

July, 2021 - Aug 2021

# Freelance, Bogor

- Developing a government website for training
  - Develop with PHP and Javascript

#### CERTIFICATE

## Cyber Security Comtia cysa+

Infra Digital Foundation, South Jakarta

## **Internship Certificate**

Cyberlabs Indonesia, Bandung

## **Junior Programmer**

Badan Nasional Sertifikasi Profesi (BNSP)